http://www.larosas.com/privacy

Our Privacy Statement
We will always respect your privacy.
You are our guest, and we think of our guests as old friends. Sometimes, we ask you for personal information like name, phone number, address, email address, etc. so that we can better serve you. But, like old friends do, we promise to keep that information private and secure. Below, we explain some of the ways we collect information, and how we might use it. If you have any questions, please click on “Contact Us” on any page of larosas.com. You'll find complete contact information there.
Ways we collect information.
We get information that our guests directly share with us by phone, on the Internet, at sponsored events, or from our pizzerias.
We get information from emails our guests and visitors to our website send us.
We get information when you order from us over the phone or online (example: the pizzeria you ordered from and the items you ordered).
Personal information we ask for:
When you call LaRosa's to place a carry out or delivery order, we ask for your name, telephone number, and full street address including city, state and zip code. We use the same information when you place a carry out or delivery order at larosas.com.
If you contact us by letter, phone, or email, we will use your sender information and other information you voluntarily send us to more completely answer your questions or concerns.
We do not sell your information.
We do not sell any of your personal information to any third party. We will collect information about how our services are used (not specific to any particular guest) so that we may improve our services.
How we store your information:
We store information you give us and information we collect in our computer databases. We own the computer servers which contain the databases, and protect the information with firewalls and security gatekeepers.
We ask for your permission to communicate to you.
On our websites, you can elect to receive promotional and/or informational emails from us. When you opt in/sign up for one of our email promotion programs, we ask that you provide us with your name and valid email address. We will send you a confirmation email that you must click to confirm your subscription. We then use this information to send email messages to you.
You can limit our communication to you.
If you no longer want to receive emails, please let us know. You can opt out/unsubscribe from receiving information at any time using the “Modify My Profile” link provided at the bottom of any email you receive from us, or by emailing contact_us@larosas.com.
We may, from time to time, send non-promotional email to all of our customers to gather input and feedback on how we can provide better service (example: surveys, updates and other maintenance notices). You are under no obligation to reply or answer the questions in the email.
Our policy can change.
This is our current privacy policy, but we reserve the right to change our website and this policy at any time. If our policy changes, the information we collect under our prior policy will continue to be governed by that policy, unless we get your permission to use the information in new ways.
Question or Comments?
If you have any questions, or believe that this policy has been violated in any way, please let us know. Just click on "Contact Us" on any page of larosas.com. You'll find complete contact information there.
Other Legal Information
General:
We try to keep accurate and current information on our websites, but cannot promise that all information is always accurate. We are not liable for any direct, indirect, consequential, or punitive damages caused by use of our websites (including but not limited to viruses, omissions or misstatements).
Trademarks:
LaRosa's, Inc. owns all trademarks used on our websites. These trademarks and related property are protected under national and international laws, and are not to be reproduced or copied without our written permission. We will take all necessary action to enforce our intellectual property rights.
Copyright:
We've copyrighted all text, graphics and the layout of our websites, and they are the exclusive property of LaRosa's, Inc. All copyrighted matter is protected under national and international laws, and are not to be reproduced, copied, distributed, displayed, or transmitted in any form, without our written permission. We will take all necessary action to enforce our intellectual property rights.
Hyper-links:
Our websites may contain links to other sites that we don't maintain or are not related to LaRosa's, Inc. We make no representations about other sites you access through LaRosa's websites. Links may not be created to LaRosa's websites without our written permission.
